http://www.novavisioninc.com/pages/info_privacy_policy.html

Toggle navigation
Search
Call
NovaVision Inc.
A6. Transparent Holograms
A7. High Security Holograms (FIPS)
C5. Security Tape on Liner
C6. Certified Cargo Screening Facility (CCSF)
D9. Water Detection Label
D10. Certified Cargo Screening Facility (CCSF)
G. ID Credentials, Printers & Ribbons
G1. Visitor Badge (time expiring)
Account
Questions? Need Help?
Call 800-336-6636
Product Finder (Online Help)
Search
Product Quick Links:
A6 Transparent Holograms
A7 High Security Holograms (FIPS)
C5 Security Tape on Liner
C6 Certified Cargo Screening Facility (CCSF)
D9 Water Detection Label
D10 Certified Cargo Screening Facility (CCSF)
G ID Credentials, Printers & Ribbons Overview
G1 Visitor Badge (time expiring)
PRIVACY POLICY SUMMARY
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Our practices on the information we collect and how we use it is noted in the section below: DETAILED INFORMATION PRACTICES.
Information Sharing
We do not sell your information to third parties. We do not share your information with outside parties or services except to the extent necessary to conduct the activities indicated in this privacy statement. We do not permit outside parties or services to process or use your information for any purposes other than those stated here.
As noted elsewhere on our web site, due to the nature of its business, NovaVision regularly cooperates with law enforcement agencies. If we suspect you are involved with counterfeiting or making a fraudulent purchase, we may proactively share your information with law enforcement agencies. From time to time, law enforcement agencies request information from us, and we comply when we believe that their access to such information is justified, or when we are compelled to furnish such information.
We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described in this policy without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment to Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.
Your Access to Your Information
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
If you are covered by applicable laws or regulations that grant you the right to request access to any personal information that we may hold, or the right to be forgotten, you may request such actions via the contact information below and we will respond within 30 days. Subject to any exemptions provided by law, if you exercise your right to be forgotten, we will delete your personal data from our systems and provide you with written confirmation of the deletion.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access, making corrections, or deleting any personal data.
Compliance
Our polices and practices are designed and intended to comply with
the General Data Protection Regulation passed by the European Union in 2016, which set rules for how companies manage and share personal data.
How to Contact Us
To contact us regarding our privacy policy or for information regarding personal information, please send an email to privacy.query@novavisioninc.com. Our phone number is +1 (419) 354-1427. NovaVision's business hours are from 8:30am to 5:30pm Eastern Daylight Time.
DETAILED INFORMATION PRACTICES
How We Use Information That You Provide
We use the information you provide about yourself and your company to:
Provide products and services that you purchase or request from us
Ship orders
Communicate with you regarding your comments and questions
Provide customer service
Send order confirmations, shipping confirmations, order tracking information, invoices, billing statements, and other transactional communications
Send order follow-up emails
Send customer satisfaction surveys
In addition to storing information you provide on the internet servers where it is collected, we will store some of this information in our internal sales, customer relationship management, and shipping systems to facilitate order processing, customer service, and follow-up communication.
If you request that we ship an order to someone other than yourself, we use that third party's information only to ship the order and/or to confirm delivery.
We also use information from automated collection sources such as cookies, server logs, security auditing applications, web site analytics applications, and tracking technologies. This information is gathered to aid in the understanding of the ways visitors access and use our web site, which helps us determine web site usage volume and patterns over various time periods. It also enables us to make improvements, to troubleshoot problems, and to identify sources of possible information security threats, fraud, and other unlawful activities. Data from automated sources is retained for limited periods of time ranging from days to several years.
We use information such as public IP address, browser, operating system, and date and time to track usage of our web site and to help us improve our web site. We do not tie this information to individual users, but use it in aggregate form for statistical purposes.
Information That We Collect
Personal information that we collect and possibly store, when you decide to provide it, includes:
Name
Company name
Job title
Postal address
Shipping address
Email address
User ID
Phone numbers
Fax numbers
Payment information, including credit card numbers or other banking information
Password
Order information, including order numbers, PO numbers, and items purchased
Personal information that we collect from automated sources such as cookies, server logs, security auditing applications, and other tracking technologies:
Your public IP address
Access times
Browser type and version
Operating system and version
Device information, such as make and model of the device used to access our web site
Web pages visited
Cookies
Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by your web browser. They facilitate some of the features of our web site.
Users from EU member countries will be presented with an option to consent to the use of cookies, and will be presented with options to decline the use of some cookies. Some aspects of our web site will not work properly without specific cookies, so-called "essential cookies." To avoid essential cookies, users should disable cookies in their web browser. Due to the ever-changing variety of web browsers, we cannot offer instructions here for disabling cookies for all browsers; your browser's built-in help or support features would be a good place to find that information. Following is a list of cookies or other tracking technologies that you may encounter due to your online interactions with NovaVision.
Essential Cookies
Essential cookies are used by our website to serve content and assist in the functioning of our shopping cart.
Our web site will not function properly without these cookies.
These cookies are not optional.
Provider Domain(s)
Cookie Name(s)
More Information
novavisioninc.com
www.novavisioninc.com
add_to_cart
ccConsentUser
form_key
guest-view
login_redirect
X-Magento-Vary
These cookies are required for our site to function as expected, providing content and ecommerce features.
paypalobjects.com
PYPF
This cookie is required to enable Paypal as a payment option.
Analytics Cookies
These cookies integrate with Google Analytics, and allow NovaVision to monitor site usage trends in order to aid in improving the web site. Web site usage data is transferred to Google, and is made available to us via Google tools for analysis. This data may be used by Google for benchmarking against other web sites. NovaVision does not track individual users in Google Analytics. These cookies are not required for the proper functioning of the web site.
Provider Domain(s)
Cookie Name(s)
More Information
novavisioninc.com
_ga
_gat
_gid
_gali
https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage
https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/enhanced-link-attribution
bat.bing.com
MR
This is a Microsoft MSN 1st party cookie which we use to measure the use of the website for internal analytics.
Shopper Approved Cookies
These cookies are generated by our customer reviews provider, Shopper Approved. We display a data feed from Shopper Approved on our web site, and that data feed generates a cookie, and relies on a second cookie that is also used by our site search feature. These cookies are not required for the proper functioning of the web site.
Provider Domain(s)
Cookie Name(s)
More Information
shopperapproved.com
__cfduid
__ss
__ss_referrer
__ss_tk
_fbp
_ga
_gid
_iub_cs-81870654
https://www.shopperapproved.com/privacy.php
https://support.cloudflare.com/hc/en-us/articles/200170156-What-does-the-Cloudflare-cfduid-cookie-do-
Marketing Cookies
These cookies help us attribute activity on our web site with advertising campaigns that we run on search engines. These cookies are not required for the proper functioning of the web site.
Provider Domain(s)
Cookie Name(s)
More Information
www.novavisioninc.com
gwcc
https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us
google.com
DV
NID
https://policies.google.com/technologies/types?hl=en-US
YouTube Cookies
Our videos are hosted on YouTube. If you play a video on our web site, YouTube will serve these cookies. These cookies are not required for the proper functioning of the web site.
Provider Domain(s)
Cookie Name(s)
More Information
youtube.com
1P_JAR
DSID
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
YSC
yt-remote-connected-devices
yt-remote-device-id
https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us
doubleclick.net
IDE
https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us
Cookie Control Cookies
These cookies are generated by CIVIC's Cookie Control application, which provides controls to European Union users to toggle cookies on our site. This data is only used to determine if the other optional cookie categories listed in the privacy policy have been accepted by the user. These cookies are not required for the proper functioning of the web site.
Provider Domain(s)
Cookie Name(s)
More Information
novavisioninc.com
analytics
reviews
videos
These cookies are used with CIVIC's Cookie Control to determine if European Union users have accepted the use of our optional cookie categories.
MailChimp Tracking Pixel
Some of our order follow-up emails are sent via an automated system.
We use MailChimp’s Mandrill service to deliver these automated emails. All of these automated emails will be related to a specific order that you placed with NovaVision. They will contain unsubscribe links in case you want to notify us that you do not want to receive them in the future.
If you open an order follow-up email from us, it may contain an invisible single-pixel image called a “beacon” that will allow MailChimp to detect when an email has been opened, or a link in the email has been clicked. MailChimp transfers this open and click information to us so that we can correlate it to existing information in our systems in order to understand whether users are responding to our email communications.
Can't Find What You're Looking For? Try our Application Search
Copyright © 1999-2020 NovaVision Inc.
Toll Free: 800-336-6636 | Site Map
Privacy Policy
Questions? Need Help?
Questions? Need Help?
800-336-6636
